

- +351 927 555 500
- drutsuldmytro@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmytro-drutsul-05a3b2217/
- Calçada do Carrascal 192, 2. Lisboa, Portugal

## **EDUCATION**

Development of Multimedia Products - Higher Professional Technical Courses (CTeSP)

2018-2019

Management IT Technician

Escola Secundária de Camões 2015-2018

## **SKILLS**

- Computer literate
- Other languages
- Problem-solving
- Adaptability
- Marketing
- Analytical thinking
- Self-discipline

# **DMYTRO DRUTSUL**

IT Technician

# **ABOUT ME**

A 23 year old tech guy with lots of enthusiasm and positivity. A quick learner and a proactive person who is always seeking for better outcomes by putting a lot of effort and determination into everything i'm involved in. I enjoy to ear different ideas and points of view. When it come to work I'm a problem-solver with a critical-thinking, who tries to be as independed as possible without sacrificing my productivity.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

IT Technician

2023 - present

#### Nation School of Public Health, NOVA - Lisbon

At the moment, ... here are some of mine responsabilities:

- IT support / Sys admin / LMS / Remote Support
- Maintance, installation and configuration of ICT equipament

**AV Technician** 

2022 - present

#### Your Jukebox - Lisbon (Freelance)

- Events, parties and social causes organizer
- Light jockey

IT Technician

2019 - 2023

#### Faculdade de Ciências Sociais e Humanas, NOVA - Lisbon

- IT support / Sys admin / LMS / Remote Support
- Maintance, installation and configuration of ICT equipament

# **LANGUAGES**

PORTUGUESE FLUENT . UKRANIAN FLUENT

ENGLISH C1

## **HOBBIES**

- I'm likely to be seen in the gym around 6 time a week.
- Love to travel, dining out and spend quality time with my closest people